https://www.authenticwindow.com/privacy-policy/

Schedule a free consultation:
914.644.4800
Search for:
Schedule a free consultation:
914.644.4800
Search for:
FREE CONSULTATION
Schedule Free consultation with an Authentic Window Design expert. Complete the form below and one of our expert staff will connect you.
State
Select OneAlabamaAlaskaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareFloridaGeorgiaHawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaOhioOklahomaOregonPennsylvaniaRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVermontVirginiaWashingtonDistrict of ColumbiaWest VirginiaWisconsinWyoming
Zip
Video Conference Type
Select OneZOOMFaceTimeNo thanks, phone is fine
Comments
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy Of Authentic Window Design
Your Privacy
Thank you for visiting authenticwindow.lawmarketingny.com. This notice explains our online information collection and use practices and the choices you can make about the way we use and share such information. Please take the time to read and understand this policy so that you can understand how we use your personal information. OUR ONLINE INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE PRACTICES MAY DIFFER FROM OUR PRACTICES REGARDING INFORMATION OBTAINED OFFLINE. The guidelines contained herein only apply to your visits to authenticwindow.lawmarketingny.com, an Internet site owned and operated by Authentic Window Design.
The Information We Collect
At authenticwindow.lawmarketingny.com you can do a variety of things! You may be able to request information about our services or participate in surveys. The types of personally identifiable information (i.e. information that can directly identify you or indicate where you might be contacted) that may be collected at these pages could include: name, address, age, date of birth, sex, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number, and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs and services. You can view or change your information at any time by sending an email to info@www.authenticwindow.com.
Sometimes you can submit information about other people. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected about other people at these pages may include recipient’s name, address, age, date of birth, e-mail address, sex, telephone number and other identifying information.
We also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information (i.e. generic information that does not identify you personally) when you visit any of our web pages such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Internet Explorer, Safari), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows or Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online or Earthlink).
How We Use the Information
We will use the personal information you provide online for the purpose(s) you have submitted. Examples of us using your personal information for the purpose(s) submitted include if you request information about our services, we may send to you information in the mail. In addition, we may send to you an e-mail offering products or services which we think you may be interested in or to ask you to participate in a survey. For example, we may send to you an e-mail regarding special offers and announcements about our products or services. We may also contact you offline. For example, when you provide your mailing address, we may send to you in the mail information about special offers and promotions, which we think may be of interest to you. If you want us to stop using the personal information you provided in these ways, please contact us at info@www.authenticwindow.com.
How We Share Your Personal Information
We may share the personal information you provide for a variety of reasons. We may share it if it is for the purpose(s) you provided it. We may also share it as may be required by law or as we think necessary to protect our company or others from injury (e.g. in response to a court order or subpoena, in response to a law enforcement agency request or when we believe that someone is causing (or about to cause) injury to or interference with the rights or property of another). We may also share personal information with other persons or companies with whom we contract to carry out internal site operations or our business activities (for example, sending out a product or a promotional item that you have requested on the site).
Additionally, we may share the personal information you provide online with companies not affiliated with us (i.e. third party companies) who want to market products or services to you or to ask you questions, both online and offline. If you want us to stop sharing your personal information with these companies, please click here or send an email to info@www.authenticwindow.com. You may need to communicate with such non-affiliated companies directly if you later decide that you no longer wish to receive their communications or if you wish to change any data you provided online. In this instance, any changes or amendments to your personal information must be given directly to each company who communicates with you as these changes, amendments and/or deletions will not be exchanged between us and non-affiliated companies.
If we do share personal information to a non-affiliated company, to the extent practical, we require that they protect such information in a manner that is consistent with this policy. We cannot, however, guarantee how these non-affiliated companies will use your personal information.
Use and Disclosure of Anonymous Information
We sometimes use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze how our site is used, as well as to offer you products, programs or services. Sometimes we share aggregate information with others, including affiliated companies and non-affiliated companies.
Cookies
To enhance your online experience with us, we may use "cookies." Cookies are text files placed on your hard disk by our web server to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us. However, once you choose to provide the personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. We may use cookies as a convenience feature to save you time, to understand how our site is used, and to improve the content and offerings on our site. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our web pages or recall your specific information on subsequent visits (e.g. to recognize you by name when you return to our site). We also may use cookies to offer you products, programs or services. You can opt to have your browser reject cookies. If you do that, you may need to re-register with us every time you visit our site in order to participate in certain promotions and other stuff. You should also know that companies that advertise on our web site (and their agents) might use their own cookies. This policy does not cover how these companies use their cookies. A "cookie" is a bit of information that a Web site sends to your Web browser that helps the site remember information about you and your preferences.
"Session" cookies are temporary bits of information that are erased once you exit your Web browser window or otherwise turn your computer off. Session cookies are used to improve navigation on Web sites and to collect aggregate statistical information.
"Persistent" cookies are more permanent bits of information that are placed on the hard drive of your computer and stay there unless you delete the cookie. Persistent cookies store information on your computer for a number of purposes, such as retrieving certain information you have previously provided (e.g., passwords), helping to determine what areas of the web site visitors find most valuable, and customizing the web site based on your preferences. This site does not use session or persistent cookies. Clickstream Data. As you use the Internet, a trail of electronic information is left at each web site you visit. This information, which is sometimes referred to as "clickstream data," can be collected and stored by a web site’s server. Clickstream data can tell us the type of computer and browsing software you use and the address of the web site from which you linked to authenticwindow.lawmarketingny.com. We may use clickstream data as a form of non-personally identifiable information to anonymously determine how much time visitors spend on each page of authenticwindow.lawmarketingny.com, how visitors navigate throughout the site and how we may tailor our web pages to better meet the needs of visitors. This information will only be used to improve our site. Any collection or use of clickstream data will be anonymous and aggregate.
Supplementing Information
From time to time we may supplement information you give us with information from other sources, such as information validating your address. Thus, information we obtain through authenticwindow.lawmarketingny.com may be intermingled with and used in conjunction with information obtained through sources other than authenticwindow.lawmarketingny.com, including both offline and online sources.
Discussions and Community Tools
We may, from time to time, make chat rooms, forums, message boards, news groups and other community tools available to you. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information for other users to view and for us to use. For example, from time to time, we may use the content you write (including your name or screen name if you post it) for promotional purposes, in e-mail newsletters or elsewhere, and by using authenticwindow.lawmarketingny.com and/or these forums, message boards, news groups, and other community tools, you agree that we may do so. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information in these areas, since anyone – not just us – may use publicly posted information.
Our Commitment to Security
We believe we have in place the appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security and correctly use the information we collect online as well as offline. When your personal information is passed onto non-affiliated companies, to the extent practical, we require that they also have in place the appropriate safeguards. We cannot, however, guarantee that they do so.
How You Can Access or Correct Your Personal Information
For instructions on how you can access the personally identifiable information that we have collected about you online, or how to correct any errors in such information, please click here or send an e-mail to info@www.authenticwindow.com. To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.Transfer of Business Assets.
The personal information you provide is considered a company asset and may be included among transferred assets if Authentic Window Design or any of its assets are ever acquired by a third party.
Changes to this Policy
Because our business needs may change over time, we reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions from this policy at any time. If at any time in the future we plan to use your personally identifiable information in a way that differs from this policy, we will post such changes here. Your continued use of authenticwindow.lawmarketingny.com following the posting of any changes to this policy means you accept such changes.
Questions
If you have any questions or comments about our personal information collection and use practices or about this privacy statement, please send us an email at info@www.authenticwindow.com.
